SUMMARY

A technology enthusiast with more than twelve years of professional software development experience and a proven record of leading small to mid-size software development teams to deliver high-performing enterprise software solutions using various technologies and platforms.

EMPLOYMENT

Capital One Investing

July 2015 to Present

Senior Software Engineer (Consultant/Iconma)

Seattle, WA

- Built and delivered Refer-A-Friend platform for Marketing and Analytics guild as Technical Lead which
 is projected to bring \$15 million new assets under management for current fiscal year.
- Implemented micro service architecture, one of the first in the company, using Angular JS, ASP.NET MVC 5, C#, HTML5, CSS, jQuery, NUnit & Spec Flow test framework.
- Fully embraced dev ops responsibilities and hand build the CI/CD pipeline using GitHub, Jenkins, Nexus, Chef and infrastructure as code using AWS Cloud Stacks.

Microsoft

March 2015 to July 2015

Software Engineer IV (Consultant/Robert Half Technology)

Redmond, WA

- UI architected XBOX Ambassadors platform that enabled users to engage with Xbox community and get rewarded for it.
- Built a mobile-first and test driven web application using Bootstrap, Angular JS, ASP.NET MVC 5, C#,
 HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Karma & Protractor test suits, Xunit test framework, Web API, Moq, & Unity DI.
- Cloud software development experience using Microsoft Azure's infrastructure management tools such as cloud services, service bus topics, subscriptions, SQL server instances, and storage.

Twentieth Century Fox

June 2014 to March 2015

Lead Software Developer (Consultant/Robert Half Technology)

Seattle, WA

- Delivered a secure and large-scale Digital Asset Management System for Fox that consolidated 1 million plus digital assets into a single web portal.
- Lead and mentored a team of four developers, designed systems architecture and managed workload to align business needs.

Time Warner

October 2010 to June 2014

Expert Software Developer

Atlanta, GA

 Created scalable software products with high data quality for the strategic planning division to help monetize Time Warner's TV contents, which generates over \$4 billion advertising revenue annually.

Xerox

April 2008 to October 2010

Senior Systems Development Specialist

Atlanta, GA

• Engaged in multiple full software development life cycles of the Airport Parking Revenue Control Software System in major world airports, with an average of \$15 million revenue per implementation.

EDUCATION

Online Master of Science in Computer Science (Interactive Intelligence Specialization)

Jan 2015 to Present

Georgia Institute of Technology - College of Computing, Atlanta, GA

Professional Master of Business Administration (MBA)

May 2011

University of Georgia - Terry College of Business, Athens, GA

Bachelor of Science in Information Systems

May 2003

University of Texas, Arlington, TX